When you reviewed the film from Buffalo,
obviously made a lot of good throws, but
what stood out the most?
>> Good and bad.
>> Yeah, played pretty close to perfect.
Um,
you know, obviously would like to have
the one that that they intercepted back,
but other than that, I played pretty
good.
Do you have an idea of like uh after the
game on Sunday, you expressed an
awareness of both defenders that were in
the area obviously um but having looked
back at it now. Is there anything
you could have done differently to get
out of that play?
>> Yeah, either you know throw it higher or
um
realize something wrong is going on and
try to eat it.
All right. Thanks, guys. [laughter]
>> [music]
>> your mentality just going forward
these last four games.
>> Just try to play well, keep getting
better.
>> When you look at what you liked against
Baltimore the first time, what kind of
game?
>> We ran the ball really well. We
protected. If you do those two things,
then you're going to have some success
as a team.
>> What stands out the most about T's
toughness to you?
>> Yeah, T, we know we know what we have in
T. Um,
you know, if he can be out there, he's
going to be out there and he's going to
keep working hard to try to get better.
That's kind of guy he is.
>> How nice was it to have Cassiki out
there and making the plays that you know
he can make, but obviously it hadn't
gone his way so far this year. Yeah,
Mike
is a guy that
um he's a really smart football player,
a guy you can count on.
>> Big reason why, you know, I felt like we
really needed him back and you saw why
on Sunday.
>> When you watch the film and you see T
make the the one-hander and then Mike
over the middle making oneanders. What I
know you know they're capable of making
those plays, but what's going on in your
mind when you watch that on the All 22?
[snorts]
Yeah, playing quarterback is all about,
you know, giving your guys opportunities
to make incredible plays. That's why
those guys are are in the NFL. That's uh
what their skill set is. And as far as
quarterback wise, your job is to try to
understand each person's skill set and
you know try to put the ball in the best
position for them to maximize that.
>> I think on after the game you said you
know you learn about show.
Why is that such a big deal to you or
why do you put so much emphasis on going
out and like truly performing giving
people a show? Number one, I work hard
for it. Um, number two, this is at the
end of the day the entertainment
industry. Um,
and
I want to go out and and play well and
if you're playing well and scoring
points and winning games and it's
usually fun to watch.
>> Was this a loss that was tougher to get
over than maybe some other losses in
your career just because of everything
that happened?
>> No, I wouldn't say that. [snorts]
Do you have a favorite throw from
Sunday? Looking back at the film.
>> I wouldn't say that either.
>> After the game, you talked about um you
know, just wanting to go out there and
how much you want to kind of play kind
of how [snorts] you have a different
perspective coming off the injury. Um
that was kind of perceived maybe as a a
just a different approach in how you
maybe perceive things after the injury.
Has that changed your competitive fire
at all to go out and win? What do you
How has the injury maybe changed the way
that you view the game?
>> Um,
no, it certainly doesn't
change my desire to to win. Um,
you know, if I want to if I want to keep
doing this, I have to have fun doing it.
Uh,
you know, I've been through a lot and if
it's not fun, then what am I doing it
for? Uh, so that's the mindset I'm
trying to bring to the table.
>> How much fun are you having right now?
Is it difficult to have fun given the
season, what you've been through
physically, emotionally, all of it? Is
it tough?
>> Yeah, certainly.
>> Did you have fun playing for the I mean,
how much of it was fun before? Winning
is always fun, but in general, was it as
fun before you got hurt?
>> Did you view it that way at least?
>> No, I wouldn't say I wouldn't say I
viewed it that way. I think um
>> what was the changing point?
>> Changing point. I'm not sure. I'm not
sure there was a
a singular moment or t of time. It's
just uh reflection reflection on a lot
of
things that I've done and been through
in my career. I think
I've been through more than most and um
certainly not easy on the the brain or
the body. So, uh just trying to have fun
doing it again.
>> You talked with Josh after the game. I I
don't really recall a bunch of times
where that's the case, like after you
shower and change and everything like
that. What does that friendship mean to
you?
>> Yeah, Josh is a guy that I'd like to be
closer with. Um, every time we get
together, we have we have fun. We enjoy
talking to each other. And obviously,
life happens and you don't you're on the
same place a lot. And, you know, when
you're in the season, you're in the
season. There's not a ton of uh
back and forth. But
um
yeah, every time I get the chance to to
spend time with him, I always enjoy it.
And um I know how much respect he has
for me and he knows how much respect I
have for him. You know, he's obviously
fun to watch
and uh I look forward to continuing that
relationship and having fun watching
him.
seem you seem like there's something on
your mind. Maybe I'm reading too much
into it, but seem frustrating.
>> Um, there's just a lot of things going
on right now. A lot of things going on
right now.
>> Football related, personally,
>> all the above.
>> What did you What about Josh?
What was your first impression of him
that whole crew?
What did you make of those guys?
>> Um, I mean that's that's just uh kind of
my first taste of
anything in this world.
Those guys had fun training together,
watching tape, working out. I enjoyed
being around them.
I enjoyed hearing him talk about the
game, watching him throw it. Uh, I
enjoyed everything about it. So, um,
that was a that was a fun experience out
there.
>> You played in the elements last week,
going to play in the elements again this
week. Um, how much do you have to adapt
to that? Is there um more running plays,
more, you know, short throws? How do you
adapt?
>> We'll see what the conditions are like
on on Sunday. If it's just cold,
there shouldn't be any problem.
Obviously, wind plays a factor. If it's
really windy, uh, you have to
to think about that a little more, but
if it's just cold, there shouldn't be
any issue.
>> Zach said today, Joe, that he likes the
way the team has responded, at least
emotionally,
psychologically, in the locker room
throughout the season. Do you monitor
that clo and I understand you were away
from the team a lot, but do you monitor
that? Do you pay attention to psyche of
the locker room a lot? Yeah, I think as
a quarterback you have to. Um, you know,
like you said, I was I was away for for
nine weeks, 10 weeks. So, um, tough for
me to to really get a gauge on that
until, you know, I came back. And, you
know, since I've been back, everybody's
been great. You know, the the energy
bringers are bringing energy and, um, I
think that's been positive. We've had
good practices and we've been
competitive. [clears throat]
It sounds like Trey is not coming to be
back before the end of the year. How how
frustrating is it? Y'all never really
got to see what Trey could bring after
what he's done, not only last year,
previous four years.
>> Yeah, obviously tough. Um, you know,
he's
great great at what he does.
You saw it when when he was out there
this year. Um,
he he closed out the Jacksonville game.
you know, he was making plays
and, you know, he's he's that's what
he's done his whole career. He just gets
sacks, makes plays, and
talks smack and you need guys like that
on your team. Um, so obviously, you
know, we'd be better with him out there.
>> Is there, you know, obviously he's going
to be a free agent next year. Um, you
know, who knows what's going to happen.
Is there an element of what he brings
that y'all need in order to be an elite
defense or an elite team moving forward?
>> Yeah, obviously, you know, we're we're
better with him. We're better with him.
Um we we'll see what the offseason
brings. You never know. Uh a lot of
things can happen.
>> A lot of things have to break a certain
way over these next four weeks, but can
you speak to the importance of trying to
keep it within the locker room, keep it
within the team, and really focus on
what you guys can control? Yeah, I don't
think like you said, there's nothing.
All we can do is is focus week to week
and try to try to win games. Uh
I don't think anybody's really thinking
about the playoffs right now. That's
uh
that's
within reach but
on our fingertips. So
we just got to keep doing what we're
doing and try to get better. I think
everybody in the building knows how
talented Germaine Burton is as a
football player. How bummed were you
when it worked out the way it did?
>> Yeah, obviously tough. You know, he
shows glimpses here and there. Um but
unfortunately turned out the way it did.
>> What's uh OP meant on the offensive line
since he came over from
you a couple years now? What has he
meant to you? Yeah, consistently brings
energy,
a guy that that can bring the locker
room together and a good player. So,
when you put all that into into one
package, that's uh a guy that you want
to have on your team.
>> How well do you think the Lions been
playing the last
>> Great. They've been playing great.
>> Is it is it the best that you've been
here?
>> Yeah.
>> You didn't feel like watching that you
were able to All right. You have that
extra second almost that we're not
necessarily used to you having.
[clears throat] Did you did you feel
that in the game as well?
>> Yeah, I felt that the last two games and
you got to go and prove it every week,
but um you know those guys have have
been lights out.
>> His has T uh is there anything different
about T? I mean you haven't
talked about watch a lot of touchdowns
made some big plays. Is there anything
different about him?
No, he's he he's a guy that goes out and
produces every single year. Um,
you know, each each year is going to
work out differently as far as
production and and all that, but he's
the same player he was two years ago and
just continues to get better.
He's one of the guys that wants to get
better every day. And when you have a
guy like that, then they're going to
consistently get better throughout their
career.
>> Obviously, there's a lot of conversation
about what he's playing through and if
he, you know, sound, oh, he practiced
today as goal. [snorts] What's that like
as a as a player trying to balance, you
know, your well-being versus, you know,
knowing you want to go out there and
play as much as possible while you can
play? What's that balance like? [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's certainly something that you
have to think about. Uh,
that's that's life as a professional
athlete though. That's
no different in basketball and MMA and
baseball and that's life. That's life.
Uh, it's what we chose and
make a lot of sacrifices and your body
is often one of them.
>> Do you talk MMA with with Scott or
Dylan?
>> I have not. No, not really. I have not.
I have not.
Is there anything you like to do on your
birthday every year?
>> It always falls right in the middle of
the season, so no, not not not usually.
Go to bed early. Get some food. Normal
schedule.
>> Watch film.
>> Yeah.
>> Are there any gifts that you got from
teammates that stand out? Have you done
anything like that?
>> Uh, the old line got me a cool little
Pokemon box. So, that was sick.
>> What's in the Pokemon box?
>> I don't know. I haven't opened it yet.
[laughter]
You have a favorite Pokemon over the
years that you like particularly
>> I mean I liked Blazkin for a little bit.
Zapados, Mewtwo.
I didn't
I never liked any of the the ghost
characters very much.
Yeah, those are probably the three or
four. I'm admittedly a little lost on
Pokemon. If it's like a figurine, do you
like display it somewhere or what what
do you do with the stuff? [laughter]
>> I'll let you I'll let you research that
one.
>> Did you have a video game?
>> Uh, yeah, video games and cards. Yeah.
>> Okay. Which one did you prefer?
>> I mean, I played them all. Um, my
favorite one ever is probably Ruby.
>> Is there a card that you're most proud
of in your collection?
I've got some I got some from the from
the back in the day that are
[clears throat] uh pretty cool.
>> What do you think about the manipulation
of the marketplace for Sudo?
[laughter]
>> Uh well, I think the whole
the whole card ripping
[snorts] culture is
um definitely
a weird one. it. [snorts] Uh
I mean I've seen I don't go to the
stores, okay? But I've heard stories of
people just camped out by the restocking
areas and
wrestling each other for the boxes and
whatnot. So uh yeah, that really since
co that that space has kind of exploded,
which I think is pretty cool.
Next.